# Ar Rasyid Sarifullah Gilbijatno Frontend Developer

Kediri, Indonesia | Phone: 082264488976 | Email: arrasyidsarifullah@gmail.com

## **SUMMARY**

Frontend developer but also have a passion for design. Given that producing a modern website requires the combination of design, server technology, and the layer that users interacts with. I believe having experience in both design and development allows for making the most optimal user experiences.

### **EXPERIENCE**

## PT PUTRA JAYA COMPUTER - Trenggalek, Indonesia

IT Support (July 2019 – 30 September 2019)

- Troubleshoot, diagnosed, and resolved hardware, network, and system problems
- Providing support for Windows and Linux issues
- Gathered system information and created professional reports.

## POLITEKNIK ELEKTRONIKA NEGERI SURABAYA – Surabaya, Indonesia Network Engineer (January 2020 - March 2020)

- Configuring, installing, and managing network infrastructure related hardware and software
- Deployed and maintained Proxmox Virtual Environment with Debian Server and Ubuntu Client
- Monitoring and troubleshooting server with Zabbix

### **EDUCATION**

## UNIVERSITAS NUSANTARA PGRI KEDIRI (2021 - present)

Informatics Engineering - GPA 3.9

## **SKILLS**

- HTML
- CSS
- Tailwind CSS
- Daisy UI
- JavaScript
- React JS